Guide to the Seattle Opportunities Industrialization Center Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- PUBLICITY AND PUBLIC RELATIONS RECORDS, 1967-1985; SERIES 7
  - Photographs, 1967-1985; Subseries 2 (Box-folder 7/23 - 7/27, 7/29 - 7/39, 8/12, 9/1 - 9/3, 9/5 - 9/40, 10/1 - 10/19, 11/1 - 11/13)
    - Photo negatives (part 3 of 4), undated (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Photo negatives (part 4 of 4), undated (Box-folder 11/10)
    - SOIC "A Building of Hope" Videocassette Copy 1, 1975 (Box-folder 11/11)
    - SOIC "A Building of Hope" Videocassette Copy 2, 1975 (Box-folder 11/12)
    - SOIC Videocassette -- KIRO Presentation on SOIC, undated (Box-folder 11/13)
- PLANNING AND FACILITY RECORDS, 1971-1987; SERIES 8 (Box-folder 7/1 - 7/22, 8/1-8/11)
  - Statistics on Program Participation, 1975 (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Real Estate Appraisal, 1975 (Box-folder 7/2)
  - Real Estate Appraisal Trade School Site, 1974 (Box-folder 7/3)
  - Real Estate Appraisal, 1985 (Box-folder 7/4)
  - Skills Center Addition Funding Request, 1974 (Box-folder 7/5)
  - Wick Construction Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 7/6)
  - Position Paper for White House Conference on Domestic and Economic Affairs, 1975 (Box-folder 7/8)
  - Business Plan, 1985 (Box-folder 7/9)
  - Washington Institute of Applied Technology Resolution to Purchase Building, 1987 (Box-folder 7/10)
  - Public Auction Catalog, 1987 (Box-folder 7/11)
  - Draft Relocation Plan, 1986 (Box-folder 7/12)
  - Application to Economic Development Administration for Development Facilities Grant to Finance Development and New Construction of a Skills Center -- Part 1 of 2, 1971 (Box-folder 7/13)
  - Application to Economic Development Administration for Development Facilities Grant to Finance Development and New Construction of a Skills Center -- Part 2 of 2, 1971 (Box-folder 7/14)
  - Final Report to Economic Development Administration on Technical Assistance Grant -- Part 1 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 7/15)
  - Final Report to Economic Development Administration on Technical Assistance Grant -- Part 2 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 7/16)
  - Architecture Plan for Manpower Training Center by Gabor Lorant AIA Architect, 1971 (Box-folder 7/17)
  - Appraisal of Trade School Site, 1971 (Box-folder 7/18)
  - Economic Development Administration OEDP (Overall Economic Development Program) Financing -- Internal -- Part 1 of 3, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 7/19)
  - Economic Development Administration OEDP (Overall Economic Development Program) Financing -- Internal -- Part 1 of 3, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 7/20)
  - Economic Development Administration OEDP (Overall Economic Development Program) Financing -- Internal -- Part 1 of 3, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 7/21)
  - Skill Center Construction -- Wick Construction et al regarding Minority Manpower Utilization Compliance, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 7/22)
  - Skill Center Construction -- Part 1 of 3, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Skill Center Construction -- Part 2 of 3, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Skill Center Construction -- Part 3 of 3, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Skill Center Sale of Land to SOIC, 1972 (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Skill Center Construction -- Zoning and Tax Exemption, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Seattle Model City Program -- Skill Center Construction -- Furniture and Equipment, 1974 (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Skill Center Construction Audit, 1973 (Box-folder 8/7)
  - Skill Center Construction Progress Reports, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Skill Center Internal Finance -- Part 1 of 3, 1975 (Box-folder 8/9)
  - Skill Center Internal Finance -- Part 2 of 3, 1975 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Skill Center Internal Finance -- Part 3 of 3, 1975 (Box-folder 8/11)
- PUBLICATIONS, 1974-1983; SERIES 9 (Box-folder 4/18 - 5/4)
  - Adherent: A Journal of Comprehensive Employment Training and Manpower Development, 1974 (Box-folder 4/18)
  - Adherent: A Journal of Comprehensive Employment Training and Manpower Development, 1975 (Box-folder 4/19)
  - Adherent: A Journal of Comprehensive Employment Training and Manpower Development, 1976 (Box-folder 4/20)
  - Adherent: A Journal of Comprehensive Employment Training and Manpower Development, 1977 (Box-folder 4/21)
  - Adherent: A Journal of Comprehensive Employment Training and Manpower Development, 1978 (Box-folder 4/22)
  - Adherent: A Journal of Comprehensive Employment Training and Manpower Development, 1979 (Box-folder 4/23)
  - Adherent: A Journal of Comprehensive Employment Training and Manpower Development, 1979 (Box-folder 4/24)
  - Adherent: A Journal of Comprehensive Employment Training and Manpower Development, 1980 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Adherent: A Journal of Comprehensive Employment Training and Manpower Development, 1981 (Box-folder 5/2)
  - Adherent: A Journal of Comprehensive Employment Training and Manpower Development, 1982 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - Adherent: A Journal of Comprehensive Employment Training and Manpower Development, 1983 (Box-folder 5/4)